{
    "id": "30c05e4d51684059af56de4e80601ed0",
    "title": "Commonly Confused Words And Phrases",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ............................... him that we had not paid the utility bill yet.",
            "description": "We remind someone to do something they might forget. ",
            "answers": [
                "reminded",
                "remembered",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e3fa69adff9c42ec8a0fdd6114de67aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "I'm afraid I won't ............................... his face.",
            "description": "Remember and remind have different meanings. To remind is to make someone remember. ",
            "answers": [
                "remind",
                "remember",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "864c1323940a49619301919eab0f782d"
        },
        {
            "question": "We use only the bedroom and the kitchen. ............................... of the house is empty.",
            "description": "The rest means what is left. The article 'the' is always used in this expression. ",
            "answers": [
                "Rest",
                "The rest",
                "The remains"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3c88434e4ae040469da2e118b679bd4a"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................... of the meal were lying all over the floor.",
            "description": "We can use the word remains to talk about what is left after something has been used up. ",
            "answers": [
                "The rest",
                "Rest",
                "Remains"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "057b0dfb18054e1eb16226617cd09b05"
        },
        {
            "question": "You and Peter can take four chocolates each. The rest ............................... mine.",
            "description": "When the rest refers to a plural noun, the verb is plural. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "33577de55c024d50b8653f43702d4814"
        },
        {
            "question": "Show me ............................... again.",
            "description": "We normally use the article the before same. ",
            "answers": [
                "same",
                "the same",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5003e2a0761f45279b285b7e67b6421d"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have got ............................... .",
            "description": "We use the same as before a noun or pronoun. ",
            "answers": [
                "the same problem as me",
                "the same problem like me",
                "my same problem"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4f6a6af1288b4e31acaabbe76aa013ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "That is the same man ............................... asked me for directions yesterday.",
            "description": "Before a clause we can use the same ... that / the same ... who",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d0acb0dc497947e9b0d745e213459337"
        },
        {
            "question": "'Turn left, 'I ................................'",
            "description": "We use tell when there is an object. If there is no object, we use say.",
            "answers": [
                "said",
                "told",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7f01a70e5dcd442ca7c384e267409c12"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ............................... me that she would come.",
            "description": "We use tell when there is an object. ",
            "answers": [
                "said",
                "told",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1ae59b76ab264e9b8fcde39482f3bcb6"
        },
        {
            "question": "We will ............................... that problem tomorrow.",
            "description": "When see means think or consider, a preposition is necessary before the object. ",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "see about",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a9d3992e3a0f40b490577abc77e0842c"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................... this color suits you.",
            "description": "See can be followed by if or whether. This expression has the same meaning as find out. ",
            "answers": [
                "See if",
                "Look if",
                "Watch if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ef72aa02aaf4418e91b43365abfae0c8"
        }
    ]
}